/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data5_1', {
    title: '5.1 Using Divisibility Tests Using Divisibility Tests',
    path: '5.1-using-divisibility-tests-using-divisibility-tests',
    children: [{
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 39 divisible by 10?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{F}}{\\but{NO}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>The number 10 divides evenly into any whole number which ends in a 0. Because 39 does not end with a 0, it is not divisible by 10.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 41 divisible by 10?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{F}}{\\but{NO}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>The number 10 divides evenly into any whole number which ends in a 0. Because 41 does not end with a 0, it is not divisible by 10.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 9 divisible by 7?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{F}}{\\but{NO}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>9 is not divisible by 7.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 173 divisible by 5?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{F}}{\\but{NO}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>The number 5 divides evenly into any whole number which ends in a 5 or a 0. Because 173 does not end with a 0 or 5, it is not divisible by 5.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 28 divisible by 7?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{T}}{\\but{NO}{F}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>28 is divisible by 7.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 275 divisible by 3?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{F}}{\\but{NO}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>The number 3 divides evenly into any whole number whose digits add up to a number divisible by 3. Because the digits of 275 add up to a number that is not divisible by 3, 275 is not divisible by 3.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 47 divisible by 3?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{F}}{\\but{NO}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>The number 3 divides evenly into any whole number whose digits add up to a number divisible by 3. Because the digits of 47 add up to a number that is not divisible by 3, 47 is not divisible by 3.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 181 divisible by 5?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{F}}{\\but{NO}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>The number 5 divides evenly into any whole number which ends in a 5 or a 0. Because 181 does not end with a 0 or 5, it is not divisible by 5.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 384 divisible by 2?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{T}}{\\but{NO}{F}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>The number 2 divides evenly into any even number. Because 384 is even, 2 divides into it evenly. (Rember: an even number is a number whose one\'s place is a 0, 2, 4, 6, or 8).}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 165 divisible by 2?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{YES}{F}}{\\but{NO}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>The number 2 divides evenly into any even number. Because 165 is odd, 2 does not divide into it evenly. (Rember: an even number is a number whose one\'s place is a 0, 2, 4, 6, or 8).}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
